Guide to the Paula Green papers, 1940-2013 and undated RL.11500
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Green Dolmatch, 1950-1996 and undated; 4
  - Accounts, 1950-1996 and undated; 7
    - Harwood Canadian mounted print advertisements, undated (Box 70)
    - Harwood Canadian print advertisements, 1971-1972 (Box 67)
    - Hathaway Shirts--Advertising Age, 1970 (Box 18)
    - Hathaway Shirts--Correspondence, 1970 (Box 18)
    - Hathaway Shirts--News from the Shirt Front, Spring, 1972 (Box 61)
    - Hathaway Shirts--Photographs, 1970 (Box 18)
    - Hathaway Shirts--Presentation case, undated (Box 18)
    - Hathaway Shirts--Print advertising, undated (Box 18)
    - Hathaway Shirts--Print advertising, undated (Box 67)
    - Hathaway Shirts--Print advertising and press, 1970-1996 (Box 61)
    - Hathaway Shirts--Sketch, 1971 (Box 68)
    - Hathaway Shirts--Slides, 1972 (Box 18)
    - ILGWU--75th anniversary planning, 1976 (Box 18)
    - ILGWU--Commercial copy concepts, 1976 (Box 18)
    - ILGWU--GEB (General Executive Board) report, 1977 (Box 18)
    - ILGWU--ILGWU News-History 1900-1950 (publication) (Box 68)
    - ILGWU--Presentation, George Meany Center for Labor Studies, 1977 (Box 18)
    - ILGWU--Print advertising, 1975-1978 (Box 67)
    - ILGWU--Print advertising, undated (Box 70)
    - ILGWU--Print advertising and posters (Including Unity House), 1975-1977 (Box 72)
    - ILGWU--Print advertising and press, 1975-1980 (Box 62)
    - ILGWU--Recommended Advertising Program and Schedule, 1976 (Box 18)
    - ILGWU--Talent releases, payments, 1975-1979; 3 folders (Box 18)
    - Knickerbocker (Holly Hobbie) print advertisement, 1976 (Box 67)
    - Leilani Hawaiian Rum--Correspondence, 1972-1973 (Box 18)
    - Leilani Hawaiian Rum--Print advertising, recipe book, undated (Box 69)
    - Leilani Hawaiian Rum--Print advertising, undated (Box 18)
    - Leilani Hawaiian Rum--Recipe book, undated (Box 18)
    - Ms. Magazine print advertisement, 1973 (Box 18)
    - Ms. Magazine print advertisement, 1973 (Box 67)
    - Ms. Magazine print advertisement, 1973 (Box 71)
    - National Tuberculosis and Respiratory Disease Association, 1973 (Box 18)
    - New York Department of Health--Correspondence and report, Smoking and Health, 1978 (Box 18)
    - New York Times--Home Delivery song score, 1975 (Box 69)
    - New York Times--How to Get More People to Read the New York Times Every Day, 1969 (Box 19)
    - New York Times--New York Times Home Delivery song, 1975-1987 (Box 19)
    - New York Times--Parody storyboard, 1977 (Box 19)
    - New York Times--Photographs, undated (Box 19)
    - New York Times--Photographs: Buddy Hackett, Pearl Bailey, 1973 (Box 19)
    - New York Times--Photographs: Tammy Grimes, undated (Box 19)
    - New York Times--Print advertising, undated (Box 67)
    - New York Times--Print advertising and press, 1976 (Box 19)
    - New York Times--Slides, 1974 and undated; 2 folders (Box 19)
    - New York Times--Slides: Bob Loggia, 1974 (Box 19)
    - Olmeca Tequila slides, 1973 (Box 19)
    - Paramount Chicken--Article on Pearl Bailey campaign, 1974 (Box 19)
    - Paramount Chicken--Recipe book, undated (Box 19)
    - Paramount Chicken--Research, storyboards, 1972-1976 (Box 20)
    - Paramount Chicken--Slides: Pearl Bailey, 1974; 3 folders (Box 20)
    - Richard Kuh District Attorney re-election, undated (Box 67)
    - Seagram--Four Roses whiskey print advertisements, undated (Box 59)
    - Seagram--Robbie Brown Scotch, 1972 (Box 20)
    - Seagram--Robbie Brown Scotch print advertisements, 1972 (Box 59)
    - Seagram--Robbie Brown Scotch print layout, undated (Box 70)
    - Standard Milling Company--Advertising Age, 1975 (Box 20)
    - Standard Milling Company--Correspondence and miscellaneous, 1974-1976 (Box 20)
    - Standard Milling Company--Creative presentation boards, undated (Box 70)
    - Standard Milling Company--Print advertising (Wheatena), 1976 (Box 67)
    - Standard Milling Company--Print advertising and receipe books (Heckers, Ceresota, Wheatena), undated (Box 20)
    - Subaru--Press and publicity, 1971-1973 (Box 20)
    - Subaru--Press and publicity, 1971-1991 (Box 69)
    - Subaru--Print advertising, 1971 (Box 67)
    - Subaru--Print advertising, 1971-1991 (Box 69)
    - Subaru--Print advertising, clippings, button, 1971-1991 (Box 20)
    - Subaru--Slides, 1971 (Box 20)
    - U.S. Department of Health, Education and Welfare--Anti-smoking campaign, 1971-1974 (Box 21)
    - U.S. Department of Health, Education and Welfare--Anti-smoking posters, 1974 (Box 70)
    - U.S. Public Health Service (USPHS)--Anti-smoking pamphlets, 1971-1974 (Box 21)
    - U.S. Public Health Service--Anti-smoking report, undated (Box 21)
    - U.S. Public Health Service--Contract claims, 1972-1974 (Box 21)
    - U.S. Public Health Service--Contract memos, 1970-1973 (Box 21)
    - U.S. Public Health Service--Contracts, 1970-1974; 3 folders (Box 21)
    - U.S. Public Health Service--Correspondence and miscellaneous, 1971-1976; 3 folders (Box 21)
    - U.S. Public Health Service--Finance, 1972-1973 (Box 21)
    - U.S. Public Health Service--HEW audit report, 1974 (Box 21)
    - U.S. Public Health Service--HEW Guide for Non-Profit Institutions (Cost Principles), 1970 (Box 21)
    - U.S. Public Health Service--Media contact program, 1973 (Box 21)
    - U.S. Public Health Service--Media report, 1974 (Box 21)
    - U.S. Public Health Service--Progress letters, 1971-1974 (Box 22)
    - U.S. Public Health Service--Reports, 1972-1974 (Box 22)
    - U.S. Public Health Service--Scripts, 1970-1972; 2 folders (Box 22)
    - U.S. Public Health Service--Senate hearing on childhood smoking, 1978 (Box 22)
    - U.S. Public Health Service--Staff time estimates, 1972-1974 (Box 22)
    - U.S. Public Health Service--Work file, 1973-1976; 2 folders (Box 22)
    - U.S. Public Health Service--Work plans FY1973, 1972 (Box 22)
    - Various print advertisements, 1973-1974 and undated (Box 72)
      Includes Life Extension Institute, Ms. Magazine, South Carolina Family Practice Residents Association, U.S. Public Health Service anti-smoking
  - New Business, 1971-1978 and undated; 8
    - Bantam Books, 1973 (Box 22)
    - General Foods (Tang), 1972 (Box 22)
    - Human Nature Magazine, 1978 (Box 22)
    - Mazda Motors of America, 1975 (Box 22)
    - Playtex Cross Your Heart Fiberfill Bra, 1971 (Box 22)
    - Prospect file, undated (Box 22)
    - Revlon, 1976 (Box 22)
    - Sterling Bank, undated (Box 22)
- Paula Green Advertising (PGA), 1969-2004 and undated; 5
  - General, 1975-1993 and undated; 9
    - Ads Magazine project, 1982-1983 (Box 23)
    - Correspondence and miscellaneous, 1975-1989; 10 folders (Box 23)
    - Correspondence and miscellaneous, 1990-1993; 2 folders (Box 24)
    - Cosmetics investigation, 1978-1981 (Box 24)
    - Credentials file, undated (Box 24)
    - From Japan, 1986-1987 (Box 24)
    - Job applications, 1983-1985; 2 folders (Box 24)
    - Logo and letterhead designs, 1978 (Box 69)
    - Opening party, 1981 (Box 24)
    - Pitch reel copy notes, undated (Box 24)
    - Publicity, 1976-1982 (Box 24)
    - Research: Black Population in the U.S., 1985 (Box 24)
    - Staff biographies, undated (Box 24)
    - Talent fees, payments, 1975-1982 (Box 24)
    - Talent fees, payments, 1975-1982 (Box 25)
    - Various print advertising designs and posters, 1971-1990 and undated (Oversize-folder 1)
      Includes Brooklyn Bridge poster 1983; ILGWU calendar 1990; New York Times print layouts; Philip Morris Bill of Rights Bicentennial 1990; Stanley Home Products print layouts; Subaru print layouts; Tsingtao Vodka print layouts
  - Accounts--Cardio-Fitness Centers, 1981-1987 and undated; 10
    - Copy concepts, 1987 (Box 25)
    - Corporate publications, 1985 (Box 25)
    - Correspondence, 1986-1987 (Box 25)
    - Fitness brochures, 1986 (Box 25)
    - Photographs, undated; 2 folders (Box 25)
    - Print advertising, 1981 (Box 25)
    - Print advertising, 1981 (Box 63)
    - Print advertising, 1981-1987 (Box 66)
    - Print advertising, 1981-1985 (Box 68)
    - Print advertising, 1985 (Box 72)
    - Print advertising--Negative print, 1981-1982 (Box 72)
    - Publicity, 1985 (Box 25)
    - Publicity, 1985 (Box 68)
    - Slides, undated (Box 25)
    - Some Comments on the Cardio Fitness Focus Group Studies in Chicago, 1986 (Box 25)
  - Accounts--Goya Foods, 1977-1993 and undated; 11
    - 50 year anniversary, 1985-1986 (Box 25)
    - A Lotta Colada song score, undated (Box 68)
    - Auditions, 1983 (Box 25)
    - Billings, 1990 (Box 25)
    - Caribbean cookbook (English and Spanish), undated (Box 25)
    - Cartoon, undated (Box 25)
    - Case study on introducing Goya Sazon to non-Hispanic market, 1985 (Box 25)
    - Cocina Criolla (cookbooks), 1983 (Box 25)
    - Coco Goya, 1980-1984; 3 folders (Box 25)
    - Coco Go--Promotion, 1983 (Box 26)
    - Coco Goya--Proposal, 1980-1981 (Box 26)
    - Coco Goya--Scripts, 1985-1986 (Box 26)
    - Commercial script forms, Goya Beans "Place on Your Plate", undated (Box 26)
    - Commercial shoot charts and storyboards, undated (Box 68)
    - Confirmation of health claims made in Goya advertising, 1985 (Box 26)
    - Contact reports, 1983-1987; 2 folders (Box 26)
    - Correspondence and miscellaneous, 1979-1993; 4 folders (Box 26)
    - Correspondence on recipe books, 1987-1988 (Box 26)
    - Creative--Adobo seasoning, undated (Box 26)
    - Creative--Catalog headline sheet, 1984 (Box 26)
    - Creative--Cookbook copy concepts, 1987-1988 (Box 26)
    - Creative--Cookbook copy concepts, 1987-1988 (Box 27)
    - Creative--Copy concepts, 1984-1985 (Box 27)
    - Creative--Jingle scores, 1980-1986 (Box 27)
    - Creative--Print, 1983-1990; 6 folders (Box 27)
    - Creative--Print and television, 1983 (Box 27)
    - Creative--Print and television, 1990 (Box 28)
    - Creative--Recipe books, coupons, labels, mailings, catalogs, 1984 (Box 28)
    - Creative--Sazon, non-Hispanic market, 1984-1985 (Box 28)
    - Creative--Sazon radio, rice box copy ideas, 1987 (Box 28)
    - Creative--Television, 1979-1984; 6 folders (Box 28)
    - Creative--Television, 1985-1989; 5 folders (Box 29)
    - Creative--Tomato sauce, Pina colada, 1985 (Box 29)
    - Elegant Goyas print proposal, 1983 (Box 29)
    - Goya/Buitoni co-promotion idea, undated (Box 29)
    - Goya Crosses All the Borders (Ellen Schultz), 1986 (Box 29)
    - Goya Tango score, 1984 (Box 29)
    - "Great Events" promotion, undated (Box 29)
    - Hermione Gingold, 1980 (Box 29)
    - Labels, 1980 (Box 29)
    - Lanyard, undated (Box 29)
    - Materials for Goya recipe book, 1988 (Box 29)
    - Media recommendations, 1979-1983; 2 folders (Box 29)
    - Non-Hispanic market, 1982-1984; 3 folders (Box 30)
    - Notes, 1983 (Box 30)
    - Olive Oil: Historic Healer (Tricia Reinus), 1987 (Box 30)
    - Polly-O co-promotion, 1985 (Box 30)
    - Press, 1977-1986; 4 folders (Box 30)
    - Press, 1984-1992 (Box 68)
    - Primavera Rice Mix, 1990 (Box 30)
    - Print advertising (English and Spanish), 1983 and undated; 3 folders (Box 30)
    - Print advertising (English and Spanish), 1983-1989 (Box 68)
    - Print advertising and storyboards, 1983-1991 (Box 67)
    - Product catalog, undated (Box 30)
    - Product line, undated (Box 30)
    - Promotional handouts, undated (Box 30)
    - Recipe books, 1980-1992 (Box 30)
    - Recipes, 1980-1987; 3 folders (Box 30)
    - Recipes--Ann Zekauskas, 1984 and undated; 2 folders (Box 31)
    - Research, 1986 (Box 31)
    - Rework of freezer advertisement, 1989 (Box 31)
    - Sales trends, 1984 (Box 31)
    - Salesmen presentation, 1983 (Box 31)
    - Salsa presentation, undated (Box 31)
    - Samples of recipe books, menus, etc., undated (Box 31)
    - Sazon Goya--Creative and research on non-Hispanic market, 1985-1988 (Box 31)
    - Sazon Goya--Positioning strategy for non-Hispanic market, 1984 (Box 31)
    - Slides (Box 31)
    - Spot radio, television schedules, 1986 (Box 31)
    - Storyboards, undated (Box 70)
    - Strategy for Entering the Non-Hispanic Market in New York, 1982 (Box 31)
    - Stretch-a-Dish Beans, 1980 (Box 31)
    - Tapas, 1985 (Box 32)
    - Television casting, 1988 (Box 32)
    - Tex-Mex Diet, 1985 (Box 32)
    - Zohra Lampert, undated (Box 32)
  - Accounts--House and Garden, 1981; 12
    - Copy concepts, 1981 (Box 32)
  - Accounts--ILGWU (International Ladies' Garment Workers Union), 1975-2004 and undated; 13
    - AHF Marketing Research--Awareness and Attitude Study, 1975 (Box 32)
    - AHF Marketing Research--Proposal to Determine Consumer Awareness and Attitudes Toward the ILGWU, 1975 (Box 32)
    - AHF Marketing Research--Post-Advertising Study, 1976 (Box 32)
    - AHF Marketing Research--Trend Analysis, 1977-1978; 2 folders (Box 32)
    - America the Beautiful, 1984 (Box 32)
    - America Works campaign, 1984 (Box 32)
    - Auditions, 1979-1982 (Box 32)
    - Billings and invoices, 1990 (Box 32)
    - Body by Roxanne catalog, 1992 (Box 32)
    - Budget, 1979-1985; 2 folders (Box 32)
    - Bus poster, 1983 (Box 32)
    - Calendar project, 1983-1993; 2 folders (Box 32)
    - Calendars, 1978-1983 (Box 72)
    - Campaign ideas, 1979-1982 (Box 32)
    - Campaign planning, 1986 (Box 33)
    - Campaign proposals, 1979-1984; 2 folders (Box 33)
    - Canada, 1980 (Box 33)
    - Cartoon--Adventures of the Label Monster, undated (Box 70)
    - Case studies, 1977-1978 (Box 33)
    - Casting, 1977-1982 and undated; 3 folders (Box 33)
    - Clippings, 1980-1991 (Box 33)
    - Contact reports, 1983-1988 (Box 33)
    - Continuity acceptance, clearance, 1976-1988; 2 folders (Box 33)
    - Convention Daily, 1986 (Box 33)
    - Copy concepts, 1980-1995 and undated; 10 folders (Box 33)
    - Correspondence and miscellaneous, 1976-1997; 8 folders (Box 34)
    - Correspondence--Copyright for Union Label song, 1985 (Box 34)
    - Correspondence--Wilbur Daniels, 1979-1983 (Box 34)
    - Council for American Fashion, 1990-1991 (Box 35)
    - Crafted with Pride--Summary of Research Findings, 1986 (Box 35)
    - Creative--Print (English and Spanish), 1975-1994; 6 folders (Box 35)
    - Creative--Print and radio, 1984 and undated (Box 35)
    - Creative--Print and television, 1980 (Box 35)
    - Creative--Radio, 1976-1988; 2 folders (Box 36)
    - Creative--Radio: Christmas, 1983 (Box 36)
    - Creative--Radio and print: PACE (Professional and Clerical Employees, division of ILGWU), 1989-1990 (Box 36)
    - Creative--Television, 1975-1994; 7 folders (Box 36)
    - Creative--Television: Roxanne factory, 1992; 2 folders (Box 37)
    - Creative--Television, Spanish, 1989 (Box 37)
    - Dick Morris Consultants (Survey analysis), 1987 (Box 37)
    - Dick Morris Consultants (Union Yes campaign), 1988 (Box 37)
    - Drafts, commercial copy; campaign case history, 1980-1983 (Box 37)
    - Dubois/PACE scripts, 1989 (Box 37)
    - Evelyn Dubrow roast, 1989 (Box 37)
    - Fan mail, 1976 and undated (Box 37)
    - Fashion industry, 1993 (Box 37)
    - Health reform campaign, 1994 (Box 37)
    - Heritage Treasures from the ILGWU Archives (publication), 1982 (Box 37)
    - Histadrut Humanitarian Award Dinner for Sol Chaikin, ILGWU, 1978 (Box 37)
    - ILGWU Convention, 1977-1986; 3 folders (Box 37)
    - ILGWU Convention, 1986 (Box 38)
    - ILGWU Convention--Wilbur Daniels, 1983-1985; 2 folders (Box 38)
    - ILGWU chorus, 1980 (Box 38)
    - ILGWU directory, 1976 (Box 38)
    - ILGWU logos, undated (Box 38)
    - Industrial homework, 1981-1989; 2 folders (Box 38)
    - Invoices, 1984-1992; 7 folders (Box 38)
    - ISCI prefix, 1979 (Box 39)
    - Issue advertising, 1982 (Box 39)
    - Italian versions, 1978 (Box 39)
    - Justice (publication), 1980-1994; 2 folders (Box 61)
    - Labor press, 1980-1985 (Box 39)
    - "Look for the Union Label" French and Spanish versions, 1978-1982 (Box 39)
    - Made in America, 1992 (Box 39)
    - Media--Labor Day, 1992 (Box 39)
    - Media planning, 1979-1988; 2 folders (Box 39)
    - Media Proposals (English and Spanish), 1979-1989; 2 folders (Box 39)
    - Miss America, 1990-1991; 2 folders (Box 39)
    - Miss America, 1991 (Box 40)
    - Model releases, 1984 (Box 40)
    - "Mr. President-Elect", 1992 (Box 40)
    - New York fashion promotion, 1991 (Box 40)
    - New York fashion sketches, undated (Box 69)
    - Opinion questionnaire, undated (Box 40)
    - Overtime talent payments, 1992 (Box 40)
    - PACE scripts, 1989 (Box 40)
    - Photographs, undated; 3 folders (Box 40)
    - Photographs, undated (Box 68)
    - Photographs--Actors, undated (Box 40)
    - Photographs--American Family Celebration, 1988 (Box 40)
    - Photographs--Atlanta auditions, 1979 (Box 40)
    - Photographs--Bus poster, undated (Box 68)
    - Photographs--Chorus, undated (Box 70)
    - Photographs--Dot Dot Dot poster, undated (Box 40)
    - Photographs--Jay Mazur, undated (Box 40)
    - Photographs--Jay Mazur, undated (Box 68)
    - Photographs--Jay Mazur and others, undated (Box 68)
    - Photographs--Neptune contact sheets, Roxanne factory, 1992 (Box 40)
    - Photographs--Poster, 1977 (Box 41)
    - Photographs--Puerto Rico chorus, undated (Box 41)
    - Photographs--Swimsuits, undated (Box 41)
    - Photographs--Unity House, 1979 (Box 41)
    - Preliminary advertising proposal, 1987 (Box 41)
    - Presentation--A Look at the Media, 1985 (Box 41)
    - Presentation--A New Tactic, 1987 (Box 41)
    - Press and publicity, 1976-1995; 7 folders (Box 41)
    - Press and publicity, 1975-2004; 2 folders (Box 69)
    - Print advertising, 1976-1978 (Box 41)
    - Print advertising, 1983-1994; 3 folders (Box 42)
    - Print advertising (English and Spanish), 1975-2004; 3 folders (Box 67)
    - Print advertising and storyboards, 1989-1992 (Box 69)
    - Print and bus card designs, undated (Box 72)
    - Prototype television commercial, 1992 (Box 42)
    - Radio, 1982-1983; 2 folders (Box 42)
    - Radio--Casting, 1979-1981 (Box 42)
    - Radio--Labor Day campaign, 1983 (Box 42)
    - Radio--Schedules, 1977-1983; 3 folders (Box 42)
    - Report to Convention, 1986-1992; 3 folders (Box 42)
    - Screen Actors Guild (SAG/AFTRA), 1977-1979; 2 folders (Box 43)
    - Script for ILGWU reel, undated (Box 43)
    - Script log, 1988-1989 (Box 43)
    - Scripts and strategy, 1984-1987 (Box 43)
    - Service Employees Union (SEIU), 1976 and undated (Box 43)
    - Sing-A-Long with the ILGWU, undated (Box 43)
    - Slides and photographs, 1976 and undated; 6 folders (Box 43)
    - Slides--Behind the Scenes, "Race Track", 1980 (Box 44)
    - Slides--Bus poster #1, 1975 (Box 44)
    - Slides--Bus poster #3, 1976; 2 folders (Box 44)
    - Slides--Bus posters, New York City, 1980 (Box 44)
    - Slides--Bus poster, Pauline Trigere, 1977 (Box 44)
    - Slides--Bus poster, School, 1978 (Box 44)
    - Slides--Buses with posters, 1977 (Box 44)
    - Slides--Car, Motorcycle, 1980 (Box 44)
    - Slides--Car, Motorcycle, 1980 (Box 45)
    - Slides--Chinatown, 1988 (Box 45)
    - Slides--Chorus III, 1978 (Box 45)
    - Slides--Chorus, Emma and Lillian, 1975 (Box 45)
    - Slides--Convention bus posters, 1980 (Box 45)
    - Slides--Daycare, 1989 (Box 45)
    - Slides--Display, 1989 (Box 45)
    - Slides--Egyptian, 1978 (Box 45)
    - Slides--ESL classes, 1989 (Box 45)
    - Slides--Eva, 1975 (Box 45)
    - Slides--Hand with ice cream cone, 1980 (Box 45)
    - Slides--ILGWU Emma and Lillian; New York Times Max Morath, 1975-1976 (Box 45)
    - Slides--Kids, 1976 (Box 45)
    - Slides--Lingerie shoot, 1977 (Box 45)
    - Slides--Location shoot Roosevelt Island, 1980 (Box 45)
    - Slides--Megaphone card, 1978 (Box 46)
    - Slides--Poster #1, 1975 (Box 46)
    - Slides--Poster #3, 1976 (Box 46)
    - Slides--Poster #4, 1976; 3 folders (Box 46)
    - Slides--Poster #5 "Dancing", 1976 (Box 46)
    - Slides--Poster #6, 1976 (Box 46)
    - Slides--Poster #7, Kids jumping rope, 1976; 3 folders (Box 46)
    - Slides--Poster: Fashion, 1976 (Box 47)
    - Slides--Poster: Magician, 1977 (Box 47)
    - Slides--Poster: Raincoat, 1979 (Box 47)
    - Slides--Poster: Violin, 1979; 2 folders (Box 47)
    - Slides--Race track, 1980; 2 folders (Box 47)
    - Slides--Retirees, 1989 (Box 47)
    - Slides--Singer, 1978 (Box 47)
    - Slides--Single, 1978 (Box 47)
    - Slides--Single girl, 3 scoops of ice cream, 1980 (Box 47)
    - Slides--Skater, 1979 (Box 47)
    - Slides--Swings, 1979; 3 folders (Box 48)
    - Slides--Three Girls, 1978 (Box 48)
    - Slides--Triple, 1978 (Box 48)
    - Slides--TV shoot, 1982 (Box 48)
    - Slides--Unity House, 1976 (Box 48)
    - Slides--Violin, bass, 1979 (Box 48)
    - Spanish language media, 1976-1990; 4 folders (Box 48)
    - Spot television, 1991-1992; 3 folders (Box 48)
    - Spot television, 1992 (Box 49)
    - Statue of Liberty, 1986 (Box 49)
    - Talent fees, payments, 1979-1991; 2 folders (Box 49)
    - "Tango" bus card, 1982 (Box 72)
    - Television, 1976-1992; 6 folders (Box 49)
    - Television--Puerto Rico (Spanish), 1979 (Box 49)
    - Television schedules, 1978-1982; 3 folders (Box 49)
    - Union Health Center Usage Survey, 1989 (Box 49)
    - Union Label score, 1975 (Box 49)
    - Union Label score, 1975 (Box 69)
    - Union Label song press, 1978 (Box 49)
    - Union League Club, 1985 (Box 49)
    - Unite: Union Label research project, 1995 (Box 50)
    - Unity House, 1977-1984; 3 folders (Box 50)
    - Wall calendar, 1989-1993 (Box 50)
    - Wedding gown campaign, 1993 (Box 50)
    - Workers Defense League--David Dubinsky memorial, 1983 (Box 50)
    - Working mothers campaign, 1992 (Box 50)
    - Working Mother Magazine, 1984 (Box 50)
  - Accounts--Israel Bonds, 1992-1994; 14
    - Bond campaign radio, 1991-1992; 2 folders (Box 50)
    - Pre-event reception, 1994 (Box 50)
    - Print advertisement, undated (Box 67)
  - Accounts--Jerusalem Post, 1991; 15
    - Listening Post radio, 1991 (Box 50)
    - Subscription selling radio, 1991 (Box 51)
  - Accounts--Life Extension Institute, 1988-1990; 16
    - Invoices, 1990 (Box 51)
    - Radio, 1988-1990 (Box 51)
  - Accounts--Marval Poultry, 1978-1983; 17
    - Brochure, recipe book, 1980-1982 (Box 51)
    - Copy concepts, 1979-1983 (Box 51)
    - Press and publicity, 1978-1979 (Box 51)
    - Print advertisement, 1979 (Box 70)
    - Storyboards, undated (Box 67)
    - Storyboards, undated (Box 71)
  - Accounts--New York Times, 1987-1988 and undated; 18
    - Cartoon, undated (Box 69)
    - Print advertising, undated (Box 69)
    - Print, New York Times/Goya co-promotion, 1987-1988 (Box 51)
    - Total Bus campaign, undated (Box 51)
  - Accounts--Pizza Motors, 1980; 19
    - Copy concepts, 1980 (Box 51)
  - Accounts--Popover Café, 1997-1999; 20
    - Correspondence and miscellaneous, 1997-1999 (Box 51)
  - Accounts--South Carolina Family Practice Residents Association, 1979; 21
    - Correspondence and miscellaneous, 1979 (Box 51)
  - Accounts--Stanley Home Products, 1979-1980; 22
    - Correspondence and miscellaneous, 1979-1980 (Box 51)
    - Print advertising, 1980 (Box 51)
  - Accounts--Sterling National Bank, 1971-1996 and undated; 23
    - 63rd anniversary, 1992 (Box 52)
    - Advertising proposal, media planning, 1985-1993; 2 folders (Box 52)
    - AEFA (Annual Economic Forecasting Awards), 1989-1990 (Box 52)
    - Annual Report, 1983-1993; 2 folders (Box 52)
    - Clippings, 1985 (Box 52)
    - Contracts and invoices, 1992 (Box 52)
    - Corporate public relations handouts, 1984-1993; 2 folders (Box 52)
    - Correspondence and miscellaneous, 1983-1995; 2 folders (Box 52)
    - Creative notes and drafts, 1981-1985 and undated (Box 52)
    - Creative notes and drafts, 1990 (Box 53)
    - Creative--Print, 1980-1996; 6 folders (Box 53)
    - Creative--Print: Sterling on Seventh, 1993-1994 (Box 53)
    - Creative--Print and radio, 1981-1984 (Box 53)
    - Creative--Radio, 1985-1995; 7 folders (Box 54)
    - Draft of message from Chairman, 1993 (Box 54)